>> Jem Young: 安全是你所做的最重要的事情之一，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Security is honestly one
of the most important things you'll do,
这与我们作为工程师的工作背道而驰
which kind of run contrary
to what we do as engineers.
我们认为，不，我的工作是造东西，把东西连接起来，
We think, no, my job is to build
things and connect things and
确保管道顺利运行一切都像这样
make sure the pipes are running
smoothly and everything like that.
但安全的问题是什么都没有你的聪明
But the thing about security is none of,
none of your cleverness, none of
您的代码，如果您没有安全性，那么不会发生任何快速的应用程序问题。
your code, none of your fast application
matters if you have no security.
因为你知道会发生什么 13 岁的孩子
Because you know what's gonna happen,
some 13 year-old is gonna come in and
擦掉你的服务器或者他跟你说我的比特币之类的
wipe your server or he said to you
mine Bitcoin or something like that.
因为他们能
Why, because they can.
正如我们在我们的博客中看到的一样。
And as we noted when
we looked at our blog.
人们一直在努力
People are trying all the time.
他们现在就在你的服务器上你在想
They're trying right now on your
server and you're thinking,
我没有什么值得的
I don't have anything worthwhile.
我要把我的 BitCoins 放在我的服务器上
I'm gonna keep my BitCoins on my server.
希望你不会
Hopefully you don't.
但人们想进入任何地方仅仅因为他们利用它来建造很多
But people wanna get in anyways just
because they use it to build lots of
邪恶的东西或者试图窃取密码信用卡信息
nefarious things or just try to steal
passwords, credit card information,
就像这样
things like that.
你永远不知道服务器上有什么
You never know what's
gonna be on a server.
所以人们只想知道他们会继续努力
So people just wanna know and
they're gonna keep trying to get in.
因此，安全是我们正在做的最重要的事情之一。
So security is one of the more
important things we're doing.
这就是为什么关于这个的整个章节。
That's why there's
an entire section on this.
尽管它是堆满的工程师
Even though it's full stack engineers,
你可能不会像你想象的那么安全
you probably won't do as
much security as you think.
有专门的人把他们的整个生命奉献给了保安
There's dedicated people that dedicate
their entire lives just doing security and
行动安全之类的东西
operations, security, things like that.
但这些都是很好的做法。
But these are good practices
to keep in top of mind.
所以安全问题就在那儿跳
So the question on security is,
jump there,
如果他们能接触到你的服务器有人会怎么做
what could someone do if they gained
just to access to your server, anybody?
如果某个人能够访问您的服务器，那么该怎么办 ?
What could someone do if they
gained access to your server?
好的盖尔
Yes, Gale?
>> 演讲者 2: 如果您重复使用密码的可怕之处，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: If you do the horrible
thing of reusing your password,
他们有你的密码
they have your password for other things.
> > Jem Young: 是的，这是一个好的，你觉得更普遍。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes, that's a good one and
that's more common you think.
我见过保安专业人员他们的密码
I've seen security professionals that
they have their password taped to their
监控，因为旧习惯很难打破，
monitor, because old
habits are hard to break,
这就是我们为什么不使用这类密码的原因。
which is why we don't even
use passwords in this class.
我们使用 SSH 密钥，因为您可以复用这些密钥，
We use SSH keys because you
while you can reuse those,
你不能偷别人的电脑或设备
you can't steal unless you physically
take someone's computer or their device.
如果用户有权访问您的服务器，还有什么可以做 ?
What else can someone do if they
have access to your server?
>> 扬声器 3: 将您的站点重定向到它们。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Redirect your site to them.
有趣的地方
Nefarious sites.
>> Jem Young: 是的，他们绝对可以的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, they can absolutely.
他们可以说，我想 bankofusa.com。
They can say, I want to bankofusa.com.
但实际上并不是网站 bankofusa.com
But it's actually not actually
bankofusa.com to site that looks exactly
因为他们可以复制您的 HTML ， CSS 和 JS。
like it because they can just
copy your HTML and CSS and JS.
每次你输入你的证件
And then everytime you
type in your credentials,
他们只是在玩吧
they're just cyphing that off.
如果你不使用  更好
Even better if you weren't using HTTPS,
他们可以把所有东西都转发到真实的真实地点
they can actually forward
everything to the actual real site.
所以那些跑现场的人不知道它坏了
So that the the people running the site
don't know that it's broken and
他们只是在偷车之间的交通
they're just stealing all
the traffic in between.
这就是所谓的中间攻击中的男人。
That is actually it's called
a man in the middle attack.
这是非常非常普遍的，在  之前，老实说，这还是很常见的。
And that's very, very common, before HTTPS
and, honestly, it's still far to common.
有更容易的方法来防止这种情况发生。
There's easier ways to prevent that.
还有别人能做什么
What else could someone do?
有什么事吗
Anything, what else?
嗯。
Yes.
>> 演讲者 2: 他们可以在您的服务器上运行自己的服务器，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: They can kind of run
their own server on your server and
直到你被禁赛
until you get banned.
然后突然之间你的腿不工作了你的 IP 被禁止了
And then all of a sudden, your legit stuff
is not working cuz your IPs are banned
像邮差之类的服务
from services like a mailbot or
something like that.
比如当人们的桥梁在吐痰世界的时候
Like when people's bridges
were spamming the world.
>> Jem Young: 是的，他们可以将您锁定在自己的服务器之外。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah,
they can lock you out of your own server.
就像所有数据和你放入的时间和代码一样
So that like all that data and
all that time and code you put in,
他们可以偷它把你锁在外面你不能把它弄回来
they can steal it and lock you out
of it and you can't get it back.
你会说， DigitalOcean 我无法进入自己的服务器。
And you'll say,
DigitalOcean I can't get in my own server.
他们会像我们无法进入你的服务器
They'll be like we can't
get in your server.
这就是你的问题伙计
That's on you, pal.
人们还能做些什么 ?
What else could people do?
我想听更多马克你有什么事吗
I wanna hear more,
Mark do you have something?
>> 扬声器 3: 擦除数据库。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Scrape your database.
>> Jem Young: 他们可以刮你的数据库，他们可以把所有
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: They can scrape your
database, they can take all that credit
卡信息或非加密密码 ( 今天) ，
card information or
unencrypted passwords which today,
在数据库中仍然保留未加密的密码。
people still leave unencrypted
password in database.
别那么做
Don't do that.
希望你永远不会在你的岗位上
Hopefully, you will never be in that
position where you have to be saving
数据库的密码。
passwords to database.
他们会成为更合格但更有资格的人
They'll be someone who
is more qualified but
互联网的大部分黑客都是被人侵入的
most of the hacks of the internet
were by people who got hacked.
因为像我这样的人知道得够危险的
Because someone like me who knows
enough to be dangerous thought,
我用 MD5 哈希
I’ll use an MD5 hash.
但我只做五次
But I'll just do it five times and
我将使用 MD5 的密码来散列密码，这是一个非常易碎的散列机制。
I'll hash a password using MD5 which
is a very breakable hashing mechanism.
我去保存它看起来很安全
And I'll save that and it looks secure.
但因为数据库没有被锁定
But because the database
wasn't locked down and
许可权没有被锁定
the permission weren't locked down.
他们进了数据库你就没事了
They got into the database and
you are like, it's okay
因为所有东西都是安全的，加密后解密。
because everything is still safe cuz it's
encrypted and then they decrypted that.
坦白说，这种情况往往比你想象的要多。
Honestly and that happens way more
often than you'd like to think.
因为有一个密码能联系到
And because there's
a password reach every other
现在看来都是由于安全问题
day now it seems like it's
all due to bad security.
这就是为什么安全才是真正重要的因为在核心
And that's why security is really,
really important because at the core,
如果你要去医院或者银行或者我不知道
if you're running a hospital or
bank or I don't know,
投资公司的人都在你手里
investment company you have
people's lives in your hands.
如果有人偷你的密码就毁了你的生活
Your life can be ruined if someone steals
your password, steals all your money or
就像你付不起租金的那样，权力就会被关起来。
something like that you can't pay rent,
the power gets shut off things like that.
所以安全真的非常重要。
So security is really, really important.
也许更常见的事情是
What's probably even more
common thing that happens when
人们的服务器被破坏了
people servers get broken into.
这只会有点棘手
This one's a little trickier.
>> 扬声器 2: 已装入请求。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Overloaded with requests.
>> Jem Young: 是的，这就是最终结果，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, so
that's the end result,
他们能做的就是把它变成僵尸网络
what they do is they could turn
into what's known as a botnet.
这就是他们安装后门的程序。
And that's just a program
that they install a backdoor.
他们什么都不会做
They won't do anything.
事实上，如果你在 Unix 上真的很棒，你可以删除所有日志。
And in fact, if you're really good in
Unix, you can delete all the logs.
所以有人可以闯进去做些事情
So someone could break in,
do a bunch of stuff,
删除显示它们中存在相当普通的日志的日志。
delete the logs that show that they
ever were there which is pretty common.
有个剧本会为你做的
There's a script that will do it for you.
然后他们就像个无声的僵尸网
And then they just turn into like a silent
botnet and they might not do anything for
几个月甚至几年
months or even years.
但当时机到来他们可以激活你的服务器
But when it comes time they can
activate your server, shut down all
然后把它变成 DDoSing 的人
the running programs and then turn
that into a way of DDoSing people.
这是分布式拒绝攻击，这意味着我可以将所有服务器和
That's distributed denial of attack, which
means I can take all of my servers and
说的是
point at, say,
netflix.com 并尝试降低已分配的大量流量。
netflix.com and try to take down
assigned level of overwhelming traffic.
绝大多数的黑客服务器都是这样做的。
That is overwhelmingly what
a lot of hack servers do.
一旦他们被侵入了
And then once they're done hacking,
有时它们会完全抹掉你的服务器
sometimes they just wipe
your servers completely.
更滑稽的是我们开始看到更多的
The more nefarious ones,
we're starting to see a lot more,
就是所谓的密码劫机或洗劫
is what is called cryptojacking or
ransoming.
他们会做的就是像你之前说的马克
So what they'll do is,
Mark like you're saying earlier,
他们会窃取你的数据库凭证他们会加密的
they'll steal your database credentials,
they'll encrypt all of them.
他们会对你的整个数据库进行加密
They'll encrypt your entire database
which is, invaluable information and
他们就会把钱卖给你
then they'll sell it back to you for
money.
因为他们加密了它并且他们只有密码
Because they encrypted it and
they only they have the password.
这种情况经常发生，特别是在医院和整个美国的城镇
That happens a lot, especially with
hospitals and entire towns in America
因为他们还拿走了他们的服务器
are getting a ransom because they
still they took over their server and
把所有东西都加密了
encrypted everything.
所以你可以说我要用数据丢 20年， 30年， 40 年
So at that point, you can say I'm gonna
lose 20, 30, 40 years with the data, or
我要支付这些人的赎金
I'm gonna pay these people ransom.
没有保证他们不会把其他东西留在你的系统里
And there's no guarantee they didn't leave
others things in your system that will
到三年后你就找不到了
pop up to three years
later that you can't find.
这些都是为了吓唬你
So all that is to scare you, and
如果有人在你的服务器上就会很吓人
deliberately cuz it's really scary
if someone gets in your server.
现在有人可以获得 root 用户了，它就在游戏结束了。
Now someone gets root access,
it's game over.
你可以用根做任何你想做的事
You can do anything you want with root,
所以我们第一件事就是去根除
which is why the first thing
we do is disable root.
但这不是万灵药。
But it's not a cure all.